ourcityradio.com 2014-05-12

# Our City Radio » Privacy Policy

By using the Website, you are accepting the practices we describe here.

Information that we collect  
When you visit the Website, you provide us with two types of information: personal information that identifies you (such as your name and email address) and non-personal information (such as your IP address and browser type) that does not identify you personally, but gives us information about your computer and about your activities on our site. This information includes your IP address, your browser type, the date and time you access the site, and the website that referred you to our site. We also collect and store information from your computer using “cookies.” A cookie is a small file stored on your computer that is tied to information about you. For example, when you sign in to your account, cookies will be used to save your email address and name so the next time you visit your account from the same computer we will “remember” your email address and name in order to make your experience faster and simpler. We may also use “web beacons,” which track your use of the Website in order to provide you with more useful information and a more personalized experience the next time you visit.

If you buy or sell a ticket or enroll in a program or special offer on the Website, we will collect financial information from you (your credit card number and expiration date, billing address, etc.).

From time to time, we also may ask you some questions about yourself (such as your interests and activities, your age, etc.) so we know how to serve you better. You don’t have to answer these questions if you’d rather not.

Finally, we also may receive information about you from third parties (such as updated delivery and address information, purchase history and additional demographic information), and we may allow third parties to display advertisements on our site. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies or “web beacons”, to collect information about people who view or interact with their advertisements on our site. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and judge their effectiveness. We do not provide any personal information about you to these third parties.

Protection; Practical Limitations  
We take appropriate security measures to help safeguard this information from unauthorized access and disclosure. For example, only authorized employees are permitted to access your personal information, and they may do so only for limited reasons. We also encrypt credit card numbers and other sensitive information before it is sent from your computer to ours. We also use firewalls to help prevent unauthorized access to your personal information.

We take precautions to ensure the security of your personal information. However, we cannot guarantee that hackers or unauthorized personnel may gain access to your personal information despite our efforts. You should note that in using the Website, your information will travel through third party infrastructures which are not under our control.

You should always take great care in handling and disclosing your personal information. For example, avoid sending personal information through insecure email. Please refer to the Federal Trade Commission’s website at http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/menus/consumer/data.shtm for information about how to protect yourself against identity theft.

Our use of your information  
In general, we may use information that we collect about you in the following ways:

* to process payment for purchases you make;

* to deliver the tickets, products and services you request;

* to enroll you in programs in which you choose to participate;

* to manage your account and provide you with customer service;

* to perform research and analyze your use of, or interest in, our products, services or content (or products, services or content offered by others on the Website);

* to communicate with you by e-mail, regular mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us, our affiliated companies or other third parties;

* to help us develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on the Website and other websites;

* to verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with contests and sweepstakes;

* to enforce our terms and conditions;

* to protect against or identify fraudulent transactions;

* to generally manage our business; and

* to perform other functions, which we will describe to you at the time we collect the information.  
We may share your non-personal information in any of the above circumstances. Also, we may share aggregated non-personal information with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for general business analysis purposes. This information does not contain any personal information.

Other websites  
Third parties have their own privacy policies that govern their use of your information. There are a number of places on the Website where you may click on a link to access other websites that don’t operate under this Privacy Policy. For example, if you click on an advertisement on the Website, you may be taken to a website that we don’t control. These third-party websites may independently solicit and collect information, including personal information, from you. Importantly, these third parties will have their own privacy policies describing how they use and disclose your personal information. Those policies will govern the use, handling and disclosure of your personal information once you or we have shared it with those third parties. If you want to learn more about other entities’ privacy practices, please review the websites of those third parties. Privacy policies are typically located at the bottom of the webpage you are visiting.

If you have any questions about how a third party handles personal information, please contact that third party directly.

If you have an account, you also may close your account at any time by contacting Our City radio customer service at customersupport@Our City radio.com. If you close your account, you will not be able to sign in to your account or access any of your personal information. However, you can open a new account at any time. If you close your account, we may still retain certain information associated with your account for analytical purposes and recordkeeping integrity, as well as to prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, enforce our terms and conditions, take actions we think are necessary to protect the integrity of the Website or to protect our users, or take other actions otherwise permitted by law.

Please note that if we have already provided information about you to third parties (for example, if we’ve already sent your information to an event provider), or if you’ve given information to a third party (for example, by clicking on a website link taking you to a third party’s website, and you provided your contact information to that third party), retention of that information will be subject to those third parties’ policies. If you receive an unwanted email from a third party, you’ll have to opt-out from receiving further emails from that party itself.

Your Options  
You can choose not to provide us with certain information. However, that may result in your not being able to use certain features of the Website because such information may be required in order to use those features. For example, in order to open an account, purchase or sell tickets, or participate in a contest, promotion or sweepstakes, your personal information will be required.

At any time, you can choose to no longer receive commercial or promotional emails from us, you will be given the opportunity to opt out of receiving such messages in the future by clicking on the link at the bottom of the email that says “unsubscribe.” It may take up to 10 days for us to process an opt-out request.

Even if you have unsubscribed from receiving promotional emails from us, we may send you other types of important e-mail communications without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. These may include, but are not limited to, customer service communications and announcements, purchase notifications and confirmations, administrative notices, and surveys.

Please note that changing information in your account or opting out of receiving promotional email communications will affect only future communications from us. If we already provided your information to a third party (such as an event provider) before you changed your preferences or updated your information, you may have to change your preferences directly with that third party as well.

User content  
We may provide areas on the Website where you can post information about yourself, communicate with others, post reviews or upload content (e.g. pictures, videos, audio files, etc.). Such postings are governed by our Terms of Service, so be sure to review them before posting. In addition, keep in mind that postings may appear on other websites or when searches are conducted on search engines on the subject of your posting.

If you post any content to the Website, by electronic mail or otherwise, we will treat it as non-confidential and non-proprietary to you. Information that is posted to the Website shall not be subject to the Privacy Policy and may be publicly displayed and disclosed and otherwise used by Our City radio or any third party in any way. By posting content to the Website, you authorize us to use or allow others to distribute, reproduce or otherwise use such content. You should not post information about yourself on the website that can be used to identify or contact you, including, but not limited to, your name, home or work address, phone numbers, email address or other such information. If you post such information, Our City radio cannot prevent it from being used in a manner that violates its Terms of Service, the law, or your personal privacy and safety.

Children’s privacy  
The Website is not intended for children under 13, and we do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. Children aged 13 or older should not submit any personal information without the permission of their parents or guardians. By using the Website, you are representing that you are at least 18, or that you are at least 13 years old and have your parents’ permission to use the Website.

Visiting our website from outside the United States  
This Privacy Policy covers the collection of information on the Website from U.S. residents. If you are visiting the Website from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated.

U.S. data protection and other laws may not be as comprehensive as those in your country. Please be assured that we take steps to ensure that your privacy is protected.

Changes to this Privacy Policy  
We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the “last updated” date at the top of this Privacy Policy. If we make any material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will notify you by sending an e-mail to the e-mail address you most recently provided us in your account, and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our website. We recommend that you check the Website from time to time to remain updated as to any changes in our privacy or other policies.

How to contact us  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information-handling practices, or if you would like to request information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties, please contact us by e-mail or regular mail at the following address:

Our City radio  
476 Stoneybrook Rd  
Newtown Pa 18940

Your California Privacy Rights  
If you are a California resident, you have the right to request information about how we share certain categories of personal information with third parties. California law gives you the right to send us a request at a designated address to receive the following information:

1\. the categories of information we disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year;

2\. the names and addresses of the third parties that received that information; and

3\. if the nature of the third party’s business cannot be determined from their name, examples of the products or services marketed.
